fotopic.net 2010-11-22

# Privacy Policy :: Fotopic.Net

By accessing or using the Fotopic.Net.com site, you agree to our Privacy Policy, as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. Fotopic.Net reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time. Your use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Privacy Policy at the time of such use. 

### Your Personal Information

When you join Fotopic.Net, we collect your name, e-mail address, and demographic information. On some of our pages you can order products, make requests and register to receive materials. The types of information collected at these pages are name, address, contact and billing information, transaction, and credit card information. 

The Fotopic.Net site also uses cookies. Cookies are small files written on your machine that help us identify members. We use them to personalize our Web site for you. More information about cookies is available here. 

We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to others. 

Under the UK Data Protection Act 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access (we are registered with the [Data Protection Registrar](http://www.esd.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/esd/search.asp), no. PZ9320333). Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you. Please note that the information you enter may be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purposes of processing by Snappy Design Ltd and its affiliates. 

### IP Address

We analyze IP addresses for system administration purposes and to gather broad demographic information. We do not link IP addresses to your computer's User ID. When you place an order using our online checkout process we record your computer's IP address with your order to help us identify fraudulent credit card use. We may share this information with the financial institution that issued the credit card with which an order was placed, or with law enforcement authorities if we determine, or are notified, that the use of the credit card was fraudulent. 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your information only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to our servers. All sensitive information (credit card) supplied by users is transmitted and protected via HTTPS protocol for encrypted transfer of data. 

We will not store your credit card information in our database unless you explicitly instruct us to do so. We reveal only the last five digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personally identifiable customer information. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you. 

It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer. 

### Disclosure with Other Suppliers

Snappy Design Ltd. maintains agreements with other suppliers for the provision of services such as printing, image retouching, and support. When you place an order through Fotopic we will pass on your name and address for the sole purpose of carrying out authorisation of the transaction and supplying you with the goods, and by placing an order you consent to this sharing of information. Our suppliers are under agreement not to use these details for any other information (including direct marketing). In any case, we provide the minimal amount of information to carry out the task. 

### Links to Other Sites

This site contains links to other sites that may offer information, products or services that may be of interest to you. Fotopic.Net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

### Questions or Comments

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the Web site, you can contact Snappy Design Ltd. via email at [info@fotopic.net](mailto:info@fotopic.net). 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also read our Terms and Conditions.
